export const quizData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Who has the highest number of centuries in international cricket?",
        options: [
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Ricky Ponting",
            "Jacques Kallis",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which country has won the most ICC Cricket World Cups?",
        options: ["Australia", "India", "West Indies", "England"],
        correctAnswer: "Australia",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Who holds the record for the fastest century in ODI cricket?",
        options: [
            "AB de Villiers",
            "Corey Anderson",
            "Shahid Afridi",
            "Chris Gayle",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "AB de Villiers",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is the maximum number of overs allowed per bowler in an ODI match?",
        options: ["5 overs", "10 overs", "15 overs", "20 overs"],
        correctAnswer: "10 overs",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which cricket stadium is known as 'The Home of Cricket'?",
        options: [
            "Lord's Cricket Ground",
            "Melbourne Cricket Ground",
            "Eden Gardens",
            "Old Trafford",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Lord's Cricket Ground",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Who was the first batsman to score a double century in ODI cricket?",
        options: [
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Rohit Sharma",
            "Chris Gayle",
            "Martin Guptill",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which country is known as 'The Black Caps' in cricket?",
        options: ["New Zealand", "South Africa", "West Indies", "Sri Lanka"],
        correctAnswer: "New Zealand",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Who is the only bowler to take 19 wickets in a single Test match?",
        options: [
            "Muttiah Muralitharan",
            "Jim Laker",
            "Anil Kumble",
            "Shane Warne",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Jim Laker",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What does LBW stand for in cricket?",
        options: [
            "Leg Before Wicket",
            "Leg Behind Wicket",
            "Line Below Wicket",
            "Length Behind Wicket",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Leg Before Wicket",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which player holds the record for the most sixes in international cricket?",
        options: ["Chris Gayle", "Shahid Afridi", "Rohit Sharma", "AB de Villiers"],
        correctAnswer: "Chris Gayle",
    },
];
